

BRUNA A. RIBEIRO

• DETAILS •

Amsterdam Netherlands 06-58851409 brrunarib@gmail.com

Date of birth 07/01/1997

Nationality

Brazilian

• SKILLS •

Python

JavaScript

Frontend Development

HTML

CSS

VS Code

Analytical and Problem-Solving skills

Git

Clean, Concise Code

Management Skills

First Aid & CPR

Leadership Skills

Customer Service

Barista

• LANGUAGES •

English

Portuguese

Spanish; Castilian

HOBBIES

Camping, Gaming, Travel.

PROFILE

I am a Full Stack Developer student at Code Institute. My previous experience was related to hospitality and logistics, and includes managing, high-end customer service, copping with tight deadlines at high standards while enjoying and having fun. Always working with a humble attitude and a willingness to learn. I am honest, driven, and passionate about getting results and helping people.

■ EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Floor Manager at Indrapura, Amsterdam

June 2023 — Present

Managed a team of 20+ employees to ensure efficient workflow and customer satisfaction.

B2B Team Leader for Tiffany & Co. at Ferrari Group, Amsterdam

October 2020 — June 2023

Part of Europe's Distribution Center's opening team.

Member of the team responsible for the Stock, with achieved 98.56% accuracy. I also process refunds, exchanges, replacements as a Return Agent. I provide training to new employees and continue to offer guidance and assistance to the team.

As an ERO(emergency responder officer), I also assist in the Health and Safety of the facility and organize evacuation drills eventually.

Promoted to B2B Team Leader for our main client, Tiffany & Co.

Food and Beverage Employee at DoubleTree by Hilton, Amsterdam

February 2020 — October 2019

High demand hotel with 557 rooms, constantly focusing on client satisfaction and consistent service.

Hostess at Cecconis's, Amsterdam

April 2019 — February 2020

Cecconi's is part of Soho House, a member's only club, in which guests can enjoy their exclusivity in a casual environment.

Host & Floor manager at MOMO Restaurant, Bar & Lounge, Amsterdam

October 2018 — April 2019

5 starts restaurant known for its high-end service. I worked as Floor manager and Hostess.

Food & Beverage Supervisor at W Hotel, Amsterdam

October 2017 — October 2018

Helping the team to meet all brand standards, Stock and requisitions. Schedule, managing and accepting hours. Quarterly performance reviews. Support and motivate the team.

I managed employee training for all new recruits over a year and offered continuous advice, guidance and mentorship on duties and best practices.

Front Desk Agent at Downtown Hotel, Amsterdam

December 2016 — October 2017

Checking guests in and out. Supervise housekeeping work.

Turndown Service at Conservatorium Hotel, Amsterdam

May 2015 — December 2016

Every guests needs are meet before hand, the incredible personalized welcome set up is made depending on the occasion.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer, Code Institute

March 2023 — March 2024

COURSES

CodeChallenge, Code Instutite

February 2023 — February 2023

AirCargo Employee, SpecialCargo

February 2023 — February 2024

BHV, Westpoort

March 2022 — March 2023

BarSmarts - Advanced Bartending, Pernod Ricard

2020 - 2020

EHBO, Rode Kruis - International Committee of the Red Cross

2020 - 2020

BHV, Enprevo

September 2018 — September 2018

¶ REFERENCES

• References available upon request